Guide to the Leonard Rosenman Papers MSS.212
Fales Library and Special Collections
Leonard Rosenman Papers
circa 1949-1990
Fales Library and Special Collections
Rosenman, Leonard
MSS.212
9 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes, and 8 oversize flat boxes
The Leonard Rosenman Papers chronicle the career of Leonard Rosenman in his roles as concert composer, pianist, film composer, and conductor from the early 1950s to 2001. The bulk of the collection consists of autograph music scores, sketches, lead sheets, musical breakdowns, and parts from music composed for concert, theatrical, and television productions.
Biographical Note
Leonard Rosenman (1924-2008), a native New Yorker, was a student of Arnold Schoenberg and Roger Sessions and Ernest Bloch. In the midst of a promising concert career, and championed by Leonard Bernstein and Aaron Copland, his roommate, and piano student James Dean, convinced him to compose the score for Elia Kazan's East of Eden (1955). He followed that success with the first 12-tone score for a major motion picture, The Cobweb (1955), and James Dean's next film, Rebel Without A Cause (1955). Representing Hollywood's "second generation" of film composers, Rosenman disengaged from the lush romantic orchestrations of his predecessors, Max Steiner and Erich Korngold. His avant-garde style embraced the aesthetics of Berg and Schoenberg - well suited to the gritty films, which soon followed - Edge of the City (1957) and the documentary-style The Savage Eye (1960); which he adapted from his twelve-tone Chamber Music #1. Rosenman founded, and co-conducted with William Kraft, his own chamber group in Los Angeles during the 1960s. His Chamber Music I, a symphony for fifteen players, was premiered at the prestigious Monday Evening Concerts in 1960. Generally credited with bringing modern-music sensibility to commercial film, he experimented and broke new ground throughout his scoring career: notably with musical silence, tone colors and atonal textures in Fantastic Voyage (1966); adapting Sioux Indian source music for A Man Called Horse (1970); and creating a bizarre Mass for Beneath the Planet of the Apes (1970).
Rosenman won two Oscars for Barry Lyndon (1975) and Bound for Glory (1976) and two Emmys for Sybil (1976) and Friendly Fire (1979). Other television scores include: The Defenders (1961), Combat! (1962) and Marcus Welby, M.D. (1969). He was Oscar-nominated for Cross Creek (1983) and Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home (1986).
Scope and Content note
The Leonard Rosenman Papers, consisting of nearly 7,800 pages, chronicle the career of Leonard Rosenman in his roles as concert composer, film and television composer, and conductor. Two-thirds of the collection consists of manuscript scores of concert works, and one third comprised of scores, sketches, orchestrations, and parts for major motion pictures. The purposes of the scores fall under the broad categories of concert music, film music, and movies for television. The collection includes various autograph materials, including autograph scores, conductor short scores, sketches, vocal and orchestral parts, and lead sheets.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Arrangement
For each film, each cue is separated by "Winds," "Strings" and "Percussion," where "Winds" consists of parts for Woodwind and Brass instruments, "Strings" consists of all string instruments, "Percussion" consists of all percussive and rhythmic instruments. The "Score" for each film consists of all Cues combined (applicable to standard as well as oversized film material). When or if these parts of the cue are large, they may expand across numerous folders and are labeled to indicate this (e.g. "Folder 1 of 3").
For concert music, each piece may be separated into individual folders under the following conditions: when it is necessary to separate by "Winds," "Strings," "Percussion" and "Score" (applicable to pieces large and small), and when the material in which it was scored differs from other copies (i.e. manuscript paper, onion skin), in which case the difference will be indicated (e.g. "Onion skin"). Oversized Concert material is organized in a similar fashion.
Folders are arranged alphabetically by title within each series. The collection is arranged into two series which have been separated by document size:
Series I. Film Scores and Parts
Series II. Concert Music
Oversize -- Series I. Film Scores and Parts
Oversize -- Series II. Concert Music
Custodial History
The Leonard Rosenman Collection was donated by Judie Rosenman and the Rosenman family in 2008. The materials in the collection were retrieved from Rosenman's music studio in his Los Angeles home. Additional materials were supplied by Scott Dunn and NYU Faculty Mike Patterson.
Additional materials were donated by the Rosenman family in 2017 and integrated into the existing collection.
Orchestral music -- Scores; Composers -- United States -- 20th century; Conductors (Music); Motion picture music -- Scores.; Motion picture music -- United States.; Rebel without a cause (Motion picture); East of Eden (Motion picture); Rosenman, Leonard
- Series I: Film Scores and Parts, 158715
  - Aftermath, Cue 1 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158716 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, Cl, BsCl, Bsn, 2 Tpt, 2 Hn
    Description: Marked with pencil
  - Aftermath, Cue 1 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158717 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Instrumentation: 3 Vla, 3 Cel, 2 Bs
    Description: Marked with Pencil
  - Aftermath, Cue 1 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 158718 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Bass Drm, Vibes, Snare Drum, Sus Cym, Piano
    Description: Unmarked
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158719 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Instrumentation: Fl/Picc, Ob, Cl, Cl/BsCl, Bsn, 2 Tpt, 2 Hrn
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158720 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 158721 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Vib, Pno
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 2: Winds, Undated; 158722 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 2: Strings, Undated; 158723 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Instrumentation: 3 Vla, 4 Cel/Bs
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 158724 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Bs Drum, Vib, Pno
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 3: Winds, Undated; 158725 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, Cl, BsCl, Bsn/ConBsn, 2 Tpt, 2 Hn
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 3: Strings, Undated; 158726 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aftermath, Cue 2 M 3: Percussion, Undated; 158727 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Vib, Bass Drum, Marimba, Pno
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158728 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, Cl, BsCl, ConBsn, 2 Tpt, 2 Hn
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158729 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 158730 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Bass Drum, Vib, Pno
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 2: Winds, Undated; 158731 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, 2 Cl, Bsn, 2 Tpt, 2 Hn
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 2: Strings, Undated; 158732 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Instrumentation: 3 Vla, 5 Cel/Bs
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 158733 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Bass Drum, Pno
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 4: Winds, Undated; 158734 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Instrumentation: BsCl, Bsn, 2 Hn
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 4: Strings, Undated; 158735 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Aftermath, Cue 3 M 4: Percussion, Undated; 158736 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Bass Drum
  - Aftermath, Cue 4 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158737 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, Cl, BsCl, Bsn, Hn
  - Aftermath, Cue 4 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158738 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Aftermath, Cue 4 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 158739 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Vib, 2 Pno/Celesta
  - Aftermath, Cue 4 M 2: Winds, Undated; 158740 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, Cl, BsCl, Bsn, 2 Hn, 2 Tpt
  - Aftermath, Cue 4 M 2: Strings, Undated; 158741 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Aftermath, Cue 4 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 158742 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Instrumentation: Vib, 2 Pno/Celesta
  - Aftermath, Cue 5 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158743 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Aftermath, Cue 5 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158744 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Aftermath, Cue 5 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 158745 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Aftermath, Cue 6 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158746 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Aftermath, Cue 6 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158747 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Aftermath, Cue 6 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 158748 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Vib, Marimba, Bass Drum, Pno
  - Aftermath, Cue 7 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158749 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, 2 Cl, Bsn, Hn
  - Aftermath, Cue 7 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158750 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Aftermath, Cue 7 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 158751 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Aftermath, Cue 8 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158752 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Aftermath, Cue 8 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158753 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Aftermath, Cue 8 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 158754 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Vib, Pno/Celesta
  - Aftermath, Cue 10 M 1: Winds, Undated; 158755 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Aftermath, Cue 10 M 1: Strings, Undated; 158756 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Aftermath, Cue 10 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 159994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Aftermath, Cue 10 M 3: Winds, Undated; 159995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Aftermath, Cue 10 M 3: Strings, Undated; 159996 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Aftermath, Cue 10 M 3: Percussion, Undated; 159997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Bass Drum, Vib, Sus Cym, Pno
  - Aftermath, Cue "Bumper": Winds, Undated; 159998 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, 2 Cl, Bsn, 2 Hn, 2 Tpt
  - Aftermath, Cue "Bumper": Strings, Undated; 159999 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Aftermath, Cue "Bumper": Percussion, Undated; 160000 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 1 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160001 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob, Cl, Hn
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 1 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160002 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Instrumentation: 3 Vln I, 3 Vln II, 3 Vla, 3 Cel, 3 Bs
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 1 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160003 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    Instrumentation: Triangle, Harp, Pno/Celesta
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 1 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160004 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 1 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160005 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    Instrumentation: 3 Vla, 3 Cel, 3 Bs
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 1 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160006 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Instrumentation: Perc, Harp, Pno
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160007 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160008 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160009 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Harp, Pno
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 3: Winds, Undated; 160010 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 3: Strings, Undated; 160011 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 3: Percussion, Undated; 160012 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Instrumentation: Perc, Harp, Timp
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 4: Winds, Undated; 160013 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 4: Strings, Undated; 160014 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 2 M 4: Percussion, Undated; 160015 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Instrumentaion: Vib, Harp, Pno
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 3 M 2 R: Winds, Undated; 160016 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 3 M 2 R: Strings, Undated; 160017 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 3 M 2 R: Percussion, Undated; 160018 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Harp, Pno/Celesta
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 4 M 1 R: Winds, Undated; 160019 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 4 M 1 R: Strings, Undated; 160020 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 4 M 1 R: Percussion, Undated; 160021 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 4 M 3: Winds, Undated; 160022 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 4 M 3: Strings, Undated; 160023 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 4 M 3: Percussion, Undated; 160024 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 5 M 1 R: Winds, Undated; 160025 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 5 M 1 R: Strings, Undated; 160026 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 5 M 1 R: Percussion, Undated; 160027 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 1 R: Winds, Undated; 160028 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 1 R: Strings, Undated; 160029 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 1 R: Percussion, Undated; 160030 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Vib, Harp, Pno/Celesta
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 2 R: Winds, Undated; 160081 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 2 R: Strings, Undated; 160082 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Instrumentation: 6 Vln I/II, 2 Vla, 3 Cel, 3 Bs
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 2 R: Percussion, Undated; 160083 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Harp, Celesta
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 3/7 MOR: Winds, Undated; 160084 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 3/7 MOR: Strings, Undated; 160085 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 6 M 3/7 MOR: Percussion, Undated; 160086 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 7 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160087 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 7 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160088 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Instrumentation: 3 Vla, 3 Cel, Bs
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 7 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160089 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 7 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160090 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 7 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160091 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 7 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160092 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160093 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160094 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160095 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160096 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Ob/Eng Hn, Cl, Hn
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160097 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160100 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Instrumentation: Timp/Vib, Harp, Pno
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 4: Winds, Undated; 160101 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 4: Strings, Undated; 160102 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 8 M 4: Percussion, Undated; 160103 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Harp, Pno/Celesta
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160104 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160105 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160106 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Harp, Pno
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160107 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160108 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Instrumentation: 3 Vln I, 3 Vln II, 3 Cel, 3 Bs
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160109 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 3: Winds, Undated; 160110 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 3: Strings, Undated; 160111 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 9 M 3: Percussion, Undated; 160112 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160113 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160114 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160115 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Description: Marked in pencil
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 2 R: Winds, Undated; 160116 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 2 R: Strings, Undated; 160117 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 2 R: Percussion, Undated; 160118 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Instrumentation: Perc, Harp, Pno/Celesta
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 3: Winds, Undated; 160119 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 3: Strings, Undated; 160120 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Instrumentation: 6 Vln I/II, 3 Vla, 3 Cel, 3 Bs
  - The Color of Evening, Cue 10 M 3: Percussion, Undated; 160121 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - East of Eden, Cue 8-1-A: Strings, Undated; 160122 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Instrumentation: 2 Vln
    Description: Only two violin parts
  - East of Eden, Scores (Folder 1 of 2), Undated; 160123 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Cues: Trailer, East of Eden Theme, Reel 1: Part 2, Reel 1: Part 2, Reel 1: Part 3, Reel 1: Part 3, Reel 1: Part 4, Reel 1: Part 4, Reel 1: Part 5, Reel 1: Part 5, Reel 1: Part 6, Reel 2: Part 2, Reel 2: Part 2, Reel 2: Part 3, Reel 4: Part 2, Reel 4: Part 2, Reel 4: Part 4, Reel 4: Part 4, Reel 4: Part 5, ,Reel 5: Part 2, Reel 5: Part 3 and Reel 6: Part 1, Reel 5: Part 3 and Reel 6: Part 1, Reel 6: Part 2 Description: Marked, red/blue crayon
    Production Number: Production Numbers: 36205 - 36215
  - East of Eden, Scores (Folder 2 of 2), Undated; 160124 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    Cues: Reel 7: Part 1, Reel 8: Part 1, Reel 8: Part 1, Reel 8: Part 1-A, Reel 8: Part 1-A, Reel 8: Part 2, Reel 8: Part 2, Reel 9: Part 1, Reel 9: Part 1, Reel 10: Part 1-B, Reel 10: Part 2, Reel 10: Part 2, Reel 10: Part 3, Reel 10: Part 3 Addendum, Reel 10: Part 3 Addendum, Reel 11: Part 1, Reel 11: Part 3 and Reel 12: Part 1, Reel 11: Part 3 and Reel 12: Part 1, Reel 11: Part 2, Reel 11: Part 2, Reel 13: Part 1, Reel 14: Part 1 and 2, Reel 14: Part 1 and 2, Reel 15
    Description: Marked, red/blue crayon, "Ray"; Reel 8: Part 1: Cornet parts taped on: "Pack up your troubles in your old kit bag", "Smiles", "It's a Long Long way to Tipperary". Percussion parts written on actual part. Lightly marked, pencil; Reel 11: Part 3 and Reel 12: Part 1: Missing pages 3 and 4.
    Production Number: 36216 – 36225; 30262
  - East of Eden: Scores, undated (Box 10, Folder 8-9, Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - East of Eden, Theme: Piano, Undated; 160125 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    Production Number: 36228
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160126 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Hn I, Hn II, Tpt I, Tpt II
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160127 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    Instrumentation: 3 Cel, 3 Bs
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160128 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Sus Cym, Bs Dr, Timp, Harp, 5 Synth/Vocal
    Description: Marked with pencil and pen
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 1 A: Winds, Undated; 160129 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    Instrumentation: Fl/Picc, Fl, Ob/Eng Hn, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Ctrbsn, 4 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tba
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 1 A: Strings, Undated; 160130 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 1 A: Percussion, Undated; 160131 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    Instrumentation: Sn Dr, Bs Dr, Piatti, Timp, Toms, Cym, Harp, Pno
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160132 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, 2 Hn, 2 Tpt
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160133 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Instrumentation: 3 Cel, 2 Bs
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 1 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160134 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Instrumentation: Bs Dr, Timp, Marimba, Harp, Pno
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 2 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160135 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Instrumentation: Fl, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, 2 Hn, Tpt
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 2 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160136 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 2 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160137 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Harp
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160138 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160139 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Instrumentation: 3 Cel, 3 Bs/Synth
    Description: Marked with pen
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160140 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Instrumentation: Harp
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 3: Winds, Undated; 160141 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Instrumentation: Alt Fl/Fl, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, 2 Hn, 2 Tpt
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 3: Strings, Undated; 160142 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 3: Percussion, Undated; 160143 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Xyl, Vib, Sn, Harp, 4 Synth/Vocal
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 4: Winds, Undated; 160144 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Instrumentation: 2 Fl, 2 Ob, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Bsn/Cntrbsn, 4 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 4: Strings, Undated; 160145 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Instrumentation: 3 Vln I, 3 Vln II, 3 Vla, 3 Cel, 2 Bs
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 4: Percussion, Undated; 160146 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Timp, Bs Dr, 4 Vocal/Synth
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 5: Winds, Undated; 160147 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Instrumentation: Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 5: Strings, Undated; 160148 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 3 M 5: Percussion, Undated; 160149 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Instrumentation: Synth
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 4 M 1 A: Winds, Undated; 160150 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 4 M 1 A: Strings, Undated; 160151 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 4 M 1 A: Percussion, Undated; 160153 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Vib, Harp, Synth
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 4 M 1 B: Winds, Undated; 160154 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Instrumentation: Alt Fl, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Hn
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 4 M 1 B: Strings, Undated; 160155 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 4 M 1 B: Percussion, Undated; 160156 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Synth
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 4 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160157 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Instrumentation: 4 Cel/Bs
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 4 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160158 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 5 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160159 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    Instrumentation: 2 Fl, Ob, Eng Hn, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, Cntrbsn, 4 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 5 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160160 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 5 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160161 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Timp, Bs Dr, Sus Cym, Harp, 4 Vocal/Synth
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 6 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160162 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    Instrumentation: 2 Fl, Ob, Eng Hn, Cl, Bs Cl, 2 Bsn, 4 Hn, 3 Tpt, 3 Tbn, Tuba
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 6 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160163 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 6 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160164 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Instrumentation: Bs Dr, Vib, Timp, Harp, 3 Vocal, Synth
    Description: Marked with pen and pencil
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 7 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160165 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Instrumentation: 2 Fl, 2 Ob, Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, 4 Hn, 3 Tpt
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 7 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160166 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Instrumentation: 6 Vln I/II, 3 Vla, 3 Cel, 2 Bs
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 7 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160167 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    Instrumentation: Vib, Timp Harp, Pno
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 8 M 1: Winds, Undated; 160168 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 8 M 1: Strings, Undated; 160169 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 8 M 1: Percussion, Undated; 160170 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    Instrumentation: Timp, Harp, Synth
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 8 M 2: Winds, Undated; 160171 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Instrumentation: Cl, Bs Cl, Bsn, 2 Hn, 2 Tpt
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 8 M 2: Strings, Undated; 160172 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Keeper of the City, Cue 8 M 2: Percussion, Undated; 160173 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    Instrumentation: Xyl, Timp, Vib, Bs Dr, Harp, Synth